Angelee OticFull Stack Developer

otic.angeleemae@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/angelee-otic

https://github.com/itsangee

Profile

With over 3 years working in a high pressured health environment, I've developed an extremely resilient work ethic and approach problems with a solutions-focused mindset. My time in operating theatres has allowed me to gain strong teamwork and communication skills. Having recently completed a coding Bootcamp, I am now looking to combine these soft skills with my new technical skills and move into a full-stack developer role where I can continue to learn and grow. I am fast-paced and adaptable, and am excited to apply my skillset to the field of Tech.

Education

Full Stack Developement, Le Wagon

July 2022 - December 2022 | London, United Kingdom

Professional Experience

Part-Time Teaching Assistant, Le Wagon, London

January 2023 - present

• Teaching new Web Development students to instill a strong understanding of the fundamentals of programming in Ruby.

Perioperative Support Worker, King Edward VII Hospital

April 2019 - present | London, United Kingdom

- A team of 3 to 6 individuals daily to prioritize patient and staff safety which able to gain my strong teamwork and communication skills
- Utilized active task management and effective communication to achieve team goals
- Served as a manual handling trainer, designing and delivering training for department at all levels
- Actively supported the Health and Safety team in promoting a positive health and safety culture
- Trained new members of the staff to ensure they were equipped with the knowledge and skills needed to perform their roles safely and effectively.

Mental Health Support Worker,

Queen's Lodge Support Living

July 2016 - May 2019 | Watford

- Led a team of 3 individuals on a daily basis, facilitating daily huddles to establish goals
- Provided assistance to patients with their daily dilemmas, with a focus on addressing mental health concerns
- Actively supported patients by coordinating appointments, filling out necessary forms, and advocating for their holistic well-being through effective communication
- Managed patients' medications, ensuring timely re-order and availability for patients
- Focused on achieving positive outcomes for patients through proactive and effective management of team and patient needs.

Projects

SeakASneaker, Web App

October 2022 - November 2022

- Our first project at Le Wagon, this e-commerce platform allows users to purchase trainers.
- Working in a team
- we were able to complete the project within a tight deadline by utilizing our skills in BootStrap, Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, Figma, Cloudinary, and Heroku.
- We implemented a database to store and manage data.
- Debugging

GimmeGolf, Web app

November 2022 – December 2022

(gimmegolf.fun)

- GimmeGolf is a golf app with social features, developed as a final project at Le Wagon.
- The app allows users to book courses with friends or other members of the community, fostering connections among individuals with a shared interest in golf.
- As a team leader, I utilized tools learned at Le Wagon and my own personal management skills to oversee the development process.
- Debugging and troubleshooting.
- This project presented an opportunity to improve communication and teamwork skills.

Skills

Ruby | Rails | Heroku | GitHub | HTML | CSS Figma/Sketch | OOP | Bootstrap | Cloudinary PostgreSQL | JavaScript | Git



Tagalog English

Interests

Running | Music | Reading

Awards

The Edward Award, King Edward VII Hospital 21st September 2021

For demonstrating the professional values of the hospital.